Guide to the Between C & D Archive circa 1983-1990 MSS.084
Fales Library and Special Collections
Between C & D Archive
circa 1983-1990
Fales Library and Special Collections
MSS.084
18 Linear Feet
Between C & D was one of the most influential literary magazines of the New York downtown scene in the 1980s, founded by Joel Rose and Catherine Texier in 1983. Taking its name from the location of Rose and Texier's apartment where it was produced--on East 7th Street between Avenues C & D on Manhattan's Lower East Side--the magazine provided one of the major downtown venues for "new fiction" of both established and emerging writers like Patrick McGrath, Dennis Cooper, Gary Indiana, Kathy Acker, Lynne Tillman, and David Wojnarowicz, to name only a few. Rose and Texier's vision for Between C & D was to support writing that deviated from conventional norms and questioned accepted standards of literature. The magazine stopped publication in 1990. The collection contains the editorial correspondence, manuscripts, and copies of Between C & D, and various related materials.
Provenance
Purchased from Joel Rose and Catherine Texier in July of 1996, the printed materials were removed and cataloged in the Downtown Collection and are listed in BobCat (a special subject heading "Downtown Writers" was given to all materials in the collection as a means of retrieving all works about downtown New York). Archival materials were sorted into series and processed later. As much as possible, the editors' original organization of the material was preserved.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open for research. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
Between C & D was started in 1983 by co-editors Joel Rose and Catherine Texier. Taking its name from the location of Rose and Texier's apartment where it was produced--on East Seventh Street between Avenues C and D on Manhattan's Lower East Side--the magazine provided one of the major downtown venues for new fiction of both established and emerging writers like Patrick McGrath, Dennis Cooper, Gary Indiana, Kathy Acker, Lynne Tillman, and David Wojnarowicz, to name only a few. Rose and Texier are themselves important writers of the downtown scene. Rose has written two novels: Kill the Poor and Kill Kill Faster Faster; Texier is the author of novels Chloe l'Atlantique, written in her native French, and Love Me Tender, in English. As the cover of Between C & D illustrates, sex, drugs, violence, danger and computers were recurring motifs throughout the life of the magazine. Rose and Texier utilized the computer technology available to them in the production of the magazine. Not only were the layouts done on an Epson computer, but each issue was individually printed in their apartment on dot-matrix printers. Each issue was then individually packed into a Ziploc bag reminiscent of those used to sell drugs in the neighborhood. Rose and Texier's vision for Between C & D was to support writing that deviated from conventional norms and questioned accepted standards of literature. Thus, much of the writing featured in Between C & D focuses on the gritty underside of urban living; often shock value is employed, and the safety of middle-class standards are attacked for their underlying hypocrisy. In 1988, Penguin published an anthology of Between C & D for its Contemporary American Fiction series that included twenty-five writers chosen by Rose and Texier to represent the magazine's scope and content. The magazine stopped publication in 1990.
Scope and Content Note
The Between C & D Archive was acquired via purchase from Joel Rose and Catherine Texier in July of 1996. The collection included a complete set of Joel's copy of the magazine with all variants, correspondence, manuscripts, posters, business files, ephemera, including the computer used for the production of the magazine, and miscellaneous printed materials. The collection was built by the editors of Between C & D, Joel Rose and Catherine Texier, themselves established writers and longtime members of the New York literary scene. The collection was sorted by Marvin J. Taylor once it arrived at NYU. Printed materials were removed and catalogued in the Downtown Collection and are listed in BobCat. A special subject heading "Downtown Writers" was given to all materials in the collection as a means of retrieving all works about downtown New York. Archival materials were sorted into series and processed later. Oversized archival materials from the various series are located in an oversize box at the end of the collection.
The Between C & D Archive comprises incoming and outgoing correspondence and business files for both the magazine and the anthology; production files for the magazine; a complete run of the magazine with all variants; manuscripts, posters, and original art; ephemera, including the computer used in the production of the magazine; disks containing the print files for the magazine, outgoing correspondence, and other related data for both the magazine and anthology; and miscellaneous printed materials. The scope of the archive is comprehensive in that it contains all records and files of the magazine and anthology kept by Joel Rose and Catherine Texier, editors of the magazine. As much as possible, the editors' original organization of the material was preserved.
SERIES DESCRIPTIONS:
Series I: Correspondence and Business Files
Series I contains three boxes of business and correspondence related materials, including administrative and financial records, manuscripts and cover art, arranged alphabetically in keeping with the original order of the files as received.
Series II: Production Files
Series II contains three boxes of production related materials for Between C & D.
Series III: Complete set of Between C & D
Series III contains two boxes of Joel's copy of the complete set of Between C & D with all variants.
Series IV: Anthology
Series IV contains one box of materials relating to the Between C & D anthology, including manuscripts, the galley, author biographies, permissions, publicity, correspondence and contracts.
Series V: Ephemera
Series V contains three boxes of Epson computer components, including the keyboard and monitor, and one box containing the floppy disks on which are located the print files for the magazine and anthology as well as back-up mailing lists, administrative forms, outgoing editorial correspondence and author biographies for the anthology, as well as two small gray boxes of stamp art used in the production of the magazine.
Series VI: Printed Material
Series VI contains one box of miscellaneous printed materials arranged alphabetically. Included are various little magazines contemporaneous with Between C & D and often containing fiction by authors that appear in Between C & D.
Oversize: A flat oversize box at the end of the collection contains oversize materials from Series I, II and IV.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading within the correspondence and manuscript series. In other series, folders are essentially alphabetically arranged with some anomalies to accommodate the various material types contained therein. The series containing issues of the magazine are arranged chronologically.
The files are grouped into six series and further subdivided into subseries for oversized materials.
Series I: Correspondence and Business Files
Series II: Productions Files
Series III: Joel's Copy with All Variants
Series IV: Anthology
Series V: Ephemera
Series VI: Printed Material
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Dennis Cooper Papers (MSS.085)
Separated Material
Printed materials were removed and catalogued in the Downtown Collection. These items are listed in Bobcat. A local subject heading "Downtown Writers" was given to all materials in the collection as a means of retrieving all works about downtown New York
Floppy disks.; Artists and community -- United States; Posters.; Magazines (Periodicals); American literature -- 20th century.; Small presses -- New York (State) -- New York.; Literature, Experimental.; Printed ephemera.; Correspondence.; Manuscripts for publication.; Scripts (documents); New York (N.Y.) |v Fiction.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; American fiction -- New York (State) -- New York.; Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) -- Fiction.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); American fiction -- 20th century.; Authors, American -- 20th century.; Business records.; New York (N.Y.).; Larue, Monique; Janowitz, Tama; Indiana, Gary; Schutt, Christine, 1948-; McGrath, Patrick, 1950-; Rose, Joel.; Pell, Derek; Olsen, Lance, 1956-; Wallace, David Foster; Texier, Catherine; Woodruff, Jay; Silverberg, Ira; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Cooper, Dennis, 1953-; Between C & D Archive; Cardoni, Ed; Tillman, Lynne; Wojnarowicz, David; Hughes, Holly
- Series I: Correspondence and Business Files
  Scope and Content note
  Series I contains three boxes of business and correspondence related materials, including administrative and financial records, manuscripts and cover art, arranged alphabetically in keeping with the original order of the files as received.
  - Subseries A:
    - Administration forms, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agents, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Art work, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Charities registration, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Checks and deposit tickets, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Computer, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CCLM (Coordinating Council for Literary Magazines), undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copyright, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Acker, Kathy), undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Addonizio, Kim), undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Ae - Al), undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Amerika, Mark), undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Ames - Bor), undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Bourdain, Anthony), undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Bow - Cam), undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Cardoni, Ed), undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Carf - Con), undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Cooper, Dennis), undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (Cr - Fil), undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (Fisher, Steve), undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (Fl - Gl), undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (Golden, Mike), undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Golds - Ha), undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (Hell, Richard), undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (Henricks-Mackerron, Denise), undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (Henry, Rick), undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (Ger - Ho), undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (Hughes, Holly), undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (I - Jak), undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence (James, Darius), undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence (Janowitz, Tama), undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence (Jo - Kal), undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence (Kasper, Michael), undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence (Kat - Lam), undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence (LaRue, Monique), undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence (Lat - Len), undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence (Leyner, Mark), undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (Li - Mi), undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (Molinaro, Ursule), undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence (Mon - Mos), undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence (Mueller, Marnie), undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence (Mul - N), undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence (Olsen, Lance), undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence (Oli - Pea), undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence (Pell, Derek), undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence (Pelt - Pet), undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence (Pintonelli, Deborah), undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence (Pittore, Carlo), undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence (Pl - Pose), undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence (Posluszny, Joanne), undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence (Post - Rom), undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence (Rose, Al Israel), undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence (Rosen - Ru), undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence (S - Schl), undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence (Schutt, Christine), undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence (Schw - She), undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence (Shields, David), undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence (Shorto, Russell), undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence (Siegle, Robert), undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence (Silverberg, Ira), undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence (Sim - Son), undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence (Sostre, Mario), undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence (Sp - Ta), undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence (Teasly, Lisa), undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence (The - Tho), undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence (Tillman, Lynne), undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence (To - V), undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence (Wallace, David Foster), undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence (Warren, C. J.), undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence (Watson, Carl), undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence (We - Wi), undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence (Wojnarowicz, David), undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence (Woodruff, Jay), undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence (Woods - Wu), undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Correspondence (Yourgrau, Barry), undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence (Zinovich, Jordan), undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence (Zivancevic, Nina), undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Correspondence (hate mail), undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Correspondence (outgoing), undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Cover art (v.1, #1), undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Cover art (v.1, #2), undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Cover art (v.1, #3), undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Cover art (v.2, #1), undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Cover art (v.2, #2), undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Cover art (v.2, #3), undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Cover art (v.2, #4), undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Cover art (v.3, #1), undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Cover art (v.3, #2), undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Cover art (v.3, #3), undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Cover art (v.4, #2), undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Cover art (v.4, #3), undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Cover art (v.5, #1), undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Cover art (v.5, #2), undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Cover art (v.5, #3), undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Cover art (v.6, #1), undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Distribution/Distributors, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Editorial correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Epson computer (correspondence and information), undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Epson computer (information), undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Fliers, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Hallwalls, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Invoices, undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - ISSN number, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Ledger, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Mailing lists, undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Manuscripts (Acker, Kathy), undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Manuscripts (Aerenson, Benjie), undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Manuscripts (Ahearn, Charlie), undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Manuscripts (Ameen, Mark), undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Manuscripts (Beach, Daytona), undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Manuscripts (Bergon, Serge; Dupont, Jean-Michel; Delacorta), undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Manuscripts (Blaushild, Lisa), undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Manuscripts (Bourdain, Anthony), undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Manuscripts (Cardoni, Ed), undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Manuscripts (Carter, Emily), undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Manuscripts (Cherches, Peter), undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Manuscripts (Daitch, Susan), undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Manuscripts (Delacorta), undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Manuscripts (Fein, Cheri), undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Manuscripts (Fisher, Steve), undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Manuscripts (Golden, Mike), undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Manuscripts (Henry, Rick), undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Manuscripts (Homes, A. M.), undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Manuscripts (Hughes, Holly), undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Manuscripts (James, Kelvin Christopher), undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Manuscripts (Kriegman, Mitchell), undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Manuscripts (McFall, Lynne), undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Manuscripts (Molinaro, Ursule), undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Manuscripts (Morales, Ed), undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Manuscripts (Reilly, Nancy O.), undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Manuscripts (Raab, Scott), undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Manuscripts (Richards, Elizabeth), undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Manuscripts (Rose, Al Israel), undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Manuscripts (Rose, Joel), undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Manuscripts (Schutt, Christine), undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Manuscripts (Shields, David), undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Manuscripts (Stein, Sheri), undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Manuscripts (Tattleman, Ira), undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Manuscripts (Teasley, Lisa), undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Manuscripts (Wojnarowicz, David), undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Manuscripts (van Gogh, Theo), undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Manuscripts (Wallace, David Foster), undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Manuscripts (Zinovich, Jordan), undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - NYSCA (New York State Council on the Arts), undated (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Old ledger and documents, undated (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - PEN American Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Phone log, undated (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Poets & Writers/Coda, undated (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Press release/foreign publicity, undated (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Press release/national publicity, undated (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Proofreading symbols, undated (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Pushcart Prize, undated (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Reading mailing list, undated (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - RJsumJs, undated (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Rising Star software, undated (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Small Press, undated (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Subscriptions (bookstore/business), undated (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Subscriptions (misc.), undated (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Subscription lists, undated (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Supplementary list of reviewers= names, undated (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Supplies, undated (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Taxes, undated (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Subseries B.
    Scope and Contents note
    Oversize
    - Liston vs. Clay poster (1964) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Series II: Productions Files
  Series II contains three boxes of production related materials for Between C & D.
  - v.1, #1, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - v.1, #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - v.1, #3; (v.1, #4 see oversize), undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - v.2, #1, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - v.2, #1, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - v.2, #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - v.2, #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - v.2, #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - v.2, #3, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - v.2, #3, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - v.2, #3, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - v.2, #3, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - v.2, #4, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - v.3, #1, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - v.3, #1, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - v.3, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - v.3, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - v.3, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - v.3, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - v.3, #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - v.4, #1, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - v.4, #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - v.4, #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - v.4, #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - v.4, #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - v.4, #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - v.5, #1, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - v.5, #2, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - v.5, #2, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - v.5, #2, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - v.5, #3, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - v.5, #3, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - v.5, #3, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - v.5, #3, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - v.6, #1, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - v.6, #1, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Series III: Joel's Copy with All Variants
  Series III consists of a complete set of Between C & D.
  - v.1, #1, var.1, 1984; Illustration by Joel Rose (punk guy with mohawk and cross earring, black outline and pink fill) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - v.1, #1, var.2, 1984; Illustration by Joel Rose ("downtown" woman with high-heels, hoop earrings, and pony tail; black outline with yellow, red and blue fill) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - v.1, #1, var.3, 1984; Illustration by Joel Rose ("downtown" person, mushroom cloud haircut, high heels, black outline with red, blue, black and orange fill) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - v.1, #1, var.4, 1984; Illustration by Joel Rose ("downtown" woman with voluminous side-hair, one hoop earring, significant cleavage and high-heels, black outline and yellow, red and pink fill) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - v.1, #2, var.1, 1984; Illustration by Rick Prol (Man with bound hands tied to a board, three daggers in mouth, anchor tattoo on shoulder. Black outline with green and brown fill). (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - v.1, #2, var.2, 1984; Illustration by Rick Prol (floating head above dilapidated ship. black outline with green, brown, red, and blue fill). (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - v.1, #2, var.3, 1984; Illustration by Rick Prol (canon and pirate with bandana and eye patch. black outline with black, brown and blue fill) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - v.1, #2, var.4, 1984; Illustration by Rick Prol (pirate submerged to his neck in water, wearing a fez and drinking from a bottle, sun in the top-left. black outline with brown, blue, green, black and yellow fill) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - v.1, #2, var.5, 1984; Illustration by Rick Prol (pirate with eyepatch wearing a bicorne hat, both legs replaced by one peg leg, planet earth in top-left. black outline with brown, grey, green, blue and pink fill) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - v.1, #3, var.1, 1984; Printing/Stamping by Orsolya Drozdik (sperms) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - v.1, #3, var.2, 1984; Printing/Stamping by Orsolya Drozdik (annotated cardiopulmonary system) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - v.1, #3, var.3, 1984; Printed/Stamped by Orsolya Drozdik (herpes simplex virus) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - v.1, #3, var.4, 1984; Stamped/Printed by Orsolya Drozdik (T4 Nucleoid containing DNA) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - v.1, #3, var.5, 1984; Stamped/Printed by Orsolya Drozdik (annotated uterus) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - v.1, #3, var.6, 1984; Stamped/Printed by Orsolya Drozdik ("nascent DNA") (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - v.1, #4, var.1, 1985; Mixed Media by David Wojnarowicz (illustration of a house broken/exploded in half, on top of an image of a dollar bill) (Box 7, Folder 16)